let questions = [
    {
        question: "/ʊə/",
        answer: "D. tour",
        options: [
            "A. allows",
            "B. beard",
            "C. loud",
            "D. tour"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɜ:/",
        answer: "C. hurdle",
        options: [
            "A. hurray",
            "B. stop",
            "C. hurdle",
            "D. bundle"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɜ:/",
        answer: "D. bird",
        options: [
            "A. many",
            "B. stead",
            "C. hairy",
            "D. bird"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/s/",
        answer: "A. circle",
        options: [
            "A. circle",
            "B. coin",
            "C. pressure",
            "D. ratio"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "/ŋ/",
        answer: "A. drunk",
        options: [
            "A. drunk",
            "B. member",
            "C. none",
            "D. normal"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "/dᴣ/",
        answer: "B. ginger",
        options: [
            "A. closure",
            "B. ginger",
            "C. machine",
            "D. prestige"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɜ:/",
        answer: "D. pearl",
        options: [
            "A. airplane",
            "B. care",
            "C. scarce",
            "D. pearl"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɜ:/",
        answer: "A. work",
        options: [
            "A. work",
            "B. one",
            "C. fort",
            "D. worn"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/k/",
        answer: "D. physique",
        options: [
            "A. cease",
            "B. choice",
            "C. knight",
            "D. physique"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɪ/",
        answer: "C. pigeon",
        options: [
            "A. seive",
            "B. police",
            "C. pigeon",
            "D. guile"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/əʊ/",
        answer: "C. mot",
        options: [
            "A. lot",
            "B. not",
            "C. mot",
            "D. got"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/eɪ/",
        answer: "B. bait",
        options: [
            "A. dimple",
            "B. bait",
            "C. nimb",
            "D. climb"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ei/",
        answer: "C. freight",
        options: [
            "A. aitch",
            "B. guise",
            "C. freight",
            "D. height"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɜ:/",
        answer: "A. earth",
        options: [
            "A. earth",
            "B. blend",
            "C. ferry",
            "D. carry"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɜ:/",
        answer: "C. herd",
        options: [
            "A. joust",
            "B. born",
            "C. herd",
            "D. catty"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɔ:/",
        answer: "A. hall",
        options: [
            "A. hall",
            "B. tough",
            "C. cough",
            "D. draught"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɔ:/",
        answer: "D. lawn",
        options: [
            "A. boot",
            "B. blood",
            "C. cot",
            "D. lawn"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɒ/",
        answer: "C. pot",
        options: [
            "A. rough",
            "B. blood",
            "C. pot",
            "D. son"
        ]
    },
    
    {
        question: "/ɪ/",
        answer: "B. wanted",
        options: [
            "A. tea",
            "B. wanted",
            "C. see",
            "D. kiosk"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɜ:/",
        answer: "B. fern",
        options: [
            "A. shoot",
            "B. fern",
            "C. funny",
            "D. cunning"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɜ:/",
        answer: "A. murky",
        options: [
            "A. murky",
            "B. pesky",
            "C. heavy",
            "D. blend"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/Ʊ/",
        answer: "B. wolf",
        options: [
            "A. cool",
            "B. wolf",
            "C. food",
            "D. who"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/i:/",
        answer: "A. kiosk",
        options: [
            "A. kiosk",
            "B. city",
            "C. milk",
            "D. sieve"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/i:/",
        answer: "D. margarine",
        options: [
            "A. bat",
            "B. leg",
            "C. bit",
            "D. margarine"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɑ:/",
        answer: "A. hard",
        options: [
            "A. hard",
            "B. glue",
            "C. hawk",
            "D. pain"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/b/",
        answer: "A. slumber",
        options: [
            "A. slumber",
            "B. plumber",
            "C. aplomb",
            "D. catacombs"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/h/",
        answer: "A. hero",
        options: [
            "A. hero",
            "B. heir",
            "C. hour",
            "D. honest"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɜ:/",
        answer: "C. word",
        options: [
            "A. sword",
            "B. blood",
            "C. word",
            "D. board"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/tʃ/",
        answer: "A. chin",
        options: [
            "A. chin",
            "B. gin",
            "C. lass",
            "D. mass"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/tʃ/",
        answer: "C. batch",
        options: [
            "A. assure",
            "B. chef",
            "C. batch",
            "D. class"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/tʃ/",
        answer: "A. culture",
        options: [
            "A. culture",
            "B. staff",
            "C. chemise",
            "D. brochure"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɔi/",
        answer: "A. coil",
        options: [
            "A. coil",
            "B. spore",
            "C. floor",
            "D. pot"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɑʊ/",
        answer: "C. low",
        options: [
            "A. blue",
            "B. call",
            "C. low",
            "D. grow"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/t/",
        answer: "C. lapped",
        options: [
            "A. grabbed",
            "B. bagged",
            "C. lapped",
            "D. mowed"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/p/",
        answer: "D. spot",
        options: [
            "A. phlegm",
            "B. pterodactyl",
            "C. psychic",
            "D. spot"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/i:/",
        answer: "C. deed",
        options: [
            "A. guitar",
            "B. sphinx",
            "C. deed",
            "D. pigeon"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɑ:/",
        answer: "C. path",
        options: [
            "A. math",
            "B. gather",
            "C. path",
            "D. mass"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɜ:/",
        answer: "D. yearn",
        options: [
            "A. clear",
            "B. clarity",
            "C. fair",
            "D. yearn"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/tʃ/",
        answer: "D. vulture",
        options: [
            "A. chimera",
            "B. chemise",
            "C. machine",
            "D. vulture"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/tʃ/",
        answer: "B. attach",
        options: [
            "A. chef",
            "B. attach",
            "C. brochure",
            "D. attache"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/e/",
        answer: "D. again",
        options: [
            "A. gain",
            "B. say",
            "C. work",
            "D. again"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɜ:/",
        answer: "A. journey",
        options: [
            "A. journey",
            "B. head",
            "C. says",
            "D. care"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɜ:/",
        answer: "B. birth",
        options: [
            "A. bed",
            "B. birth",
            "C. fear",
            "D. leer"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/æ/",
        answer: "D. mass",
        options: [
            "A. far",
            "B. rather",
            "C. father",
            "D. mass"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/æ/",
        answer: "D. lass",
        options: [
            "A. park",
            "B. giraffe",
            "C. morale",
            "D. lass"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/æ/",
        answer: "B. plaid",
        options: [
            "A. park",
            "B. plaid",
            "C. past",
            "D. afar"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/e/",
        answer: "D. says",
        options: [
            "A. hearth",
            "B. air",
            "C. surprise",
            "D. says"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "/e/",
        answer: "A. many",
        options: [
            "A. many",
            "B. serf",
            "C. earth",
            "D. plait"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "/e/",
        answer: "C. breakfast",
        options: [
            "A. fern",
            "B. worm",
            "C. breakfast",
            "D. clerk"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɑ:/",
        answer: "C. clerk",
        options: [
            "A. mass",
            "B. plait",
            "C. clerk",
            "D. pack"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɑ:/",
        answer: "B. heart",
        options: [
            "A. earth",
            "B. heart",
            "C. mass",
            "D. hearth"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/k/",
        answer: "B. chalk",
        options: [
            "A. chin",
            "B. chalk",
            "C. writes",
            "D. mass"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/d/",
        answer: "A. ladder",
        options: [
            "A. ladder",
            "B. educate",
            "C. bourgeois",
            "D. adjure"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/i:/",
        answer: "D. reach",
        options: [
            "A. bin",
            "B. check",
            "C. knit",
            "D. reach"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɑ:/",
        answer: "A. card",
        options: [
            "A. card",
            "B. mass",
            "C. plait",
            "D. plaid"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/b/",
        answer: "C. slumber",
        options: [
            "A. plumber",
            "B. comb",
            "C. slumber",
            "D. climbing"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/h/",
        answer: "C. house",
        options: [
            "A. hour",
            "B. honest",
            "C. house",
            "D. heir"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɔi/",
        answer: "A. coil",
        options: [
            "A. coil",
            "B. court",
            "C. floor",
            "D. pot"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/I/",
        answer: "B. drink",
        options: [
            "A. bee",
            "B. drink",
            "C. said",
            "D. luck"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/e/",
        answer: "C. says",
        options: [
            "A. bank",
            "B. sold",
            "C. says",
            "D. clerk"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/æ/",
        answer: "D. plaid",
        options: [
            "A. beans",
            "B. car",
            "C. barn",
            "D. plaid"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɑ:/",
        answer: "D. plant",
        options: [
            "A. mass",
            "B. math",
            "C. gather",
            "D. plant"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "/u:/",
        answer: "B. broom",
        options: [
            "A. bounce",
            "B. broom",
            "C. book",
            "D. sold"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ʊ/",
        answer: "A. look",
        options: [
            "A. look",
            "B. fool",
            "C. soon",
            "D. loom"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɔ:/",
        answer: "C. draw",
        options: [
            "A. cut",
            "B. dot",
            "C. draw",
            "D. but"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɒ/",
        answer: "C. quality",
        options: [
            "A. mall",
            "B. bought",
            "C. quality",
            "D. court"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɜ:/",
        answer: "B. churn",
        options: [
            "A. bent",
            "B. churn",
            "C. clerk",
            "D. bury"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ə/",
        answer: "C. mother",
        options: [
            "A. ten",
            "B. purchase",
            "C. mother",
            "D. choose"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ʌ/",
        answer: "A. money",
        options: [
            "A. money",
            "B. home",
            "C. gone",
            "D. donkey"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/tʃ/",
        answer: "A. chin",
        options: [
            "A. chin",
            "B. brochure",
            "C. champagne",
            "D. cache"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ʃ/",
        answer: "A. bishop",
        options: [
            "A. bishop",
            "B. catch",
            "C. measure",
            "D. say"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/e/",
        answer: "B. says",
        options: [
            "A. fair",
            "B. says",
            "C. flare",
            "D. serve"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/i:/",
        answer: "C. kiosk",
        options: [
            "A. pint",
            "B. pigeon",
            "C. kiosk",
            "D. emerge"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/a:/",
        answer: "B. half",
        options: [
            "A. frame",
            "B. half",
            "C. serve",
            "D. dam"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɜː/",
        answer: "A. heart",
        options: [
            "A. heart",
            "B. meme",
            "C. match",
            "D. earth"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɪ/",
        answer: "D. biscuit",
        options: [
            "A. flight",
            "B. flee",
            "C. police",
            "D. biscuit"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/e/",
        answer: "A. breakfast",
        options: [
            "A. breakfast",
            "B. say",
            "C. earth",
            "D. fern"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/z/",
        answer: "B. raise",
        options: [
            "A. scarce",
            "B. raise",
            "C. crass",
            "D. pizza"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/æ/",
        answer: "A. plaid",
        options: [
            "A. plaid",
            "B. car",
            "C. pass",
            "D. ajar"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɪ/",
        answer: "B. pyramid",
        options: [
            "A. feet",
            "B. pyramid",
            "C. where",
            "D. pint"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/k/",
        answer: "A. anchor",
        options: [
            "A. anchor",
            "B. chemise",
            "C. xylem",
            "D. knight"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/i:/",
        answer: "B. kiosk",
        options: [
            "A. flip",
            "B. kiosk",
            "C. hind",
            "D. favorite"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ʃ/",
        answer: "D. pressure",
        options: [
            "A. cello",
            "B. occasion",
            "C. match",
            "D. pressure"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/eə/",
        answer: "C. bear",
        options: [
            "A. hero",
            "B. real",
            "C. bear",
            "D. here"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/i:/",
        answer: "D. police",
        options: [
            "A. beauty",
            "B. famine",
            "C. beige",
            "D. police"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/e/",
        answer: "B. bury",
        options: [
            "A. describe",
            "B. bury",
            "C. journey",
            "D. needle"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/æ/",
        answer: "A. timbre",
        options: [
            "A. timbre",
            "B. pass",
            "C. rather",
            "D. afar"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɒ/",
        answer: "B. swap",
        options: [
            "A. word",
            "B. swap",
            "C. sun",
            "D. wall"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɔ:/",
        answer: "A. fall",
        options: [
            "A. fall",
            "B. nose",
            "C. block",
            "D. brother"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/u:/",
        answer: "B. mood",
        options: [
            "A. would",
            "B. mood",
            "C. grove",
            "D. put"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ʌ/",
        answer: "C. rough",
        options: [
            "A. wrath",
            "B. parlour",
            "C. rough",
            "D. cough"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ʌ/",
        answer: "C. southern",
        options: [
            "A. gone",
            "B. font",
            "C. southern",
            "D. come"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ʌ/",
        answer: "A. front",
        options: [
            "A. front",
            "B. hassle",
            "C. font",
            "D. hone"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɜ:/",
        answer: "D. journal",
        options: [
            "A. scare",
            "B. bury",
            "C. fair",
            "D. journal"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ə/",
        answer: "B. breakfast",
        options: [
            "A. say",
            "B. breakfast",
            "C. village",
            "D. hairy"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "PHone",
        answer: "D. nephew",
        options: [
            "A. reveal",
            "B. psyche",
            "C. alone",
            "D. nephew"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "kiSS",
        answer: "A. listen",
        options: [
            "A. listen",
            "B. mission",
            "C. kill",
            "D. zeal"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "piQue",
        answer: "B. chloride",
        options: [
            "A. chagrin",
            "B. chloride",
            "C. ocean",
            "D. bomb"
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "/ɜ:/",
        answer: "A. journey",
        options: [
            "A. journey",
            "B. bought",
            "C. fought",
            "D. caught"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "/u:/",
        answer: "C. food",
        options: [
            "A. good",
            "B. book",
            "C. food",
            "D. should"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "/ɜ:/",
        answer: "A. nurse",
        options: [
            "A. nurse",
            "B. help",
            "C. fair",
            "D. breakfast"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "/a:/",
        answer: "C. father",
        options: [
            "A. bat",
            "B. chat",
            "C. father",
            "D. month"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "/D/",
        answer: "C. ponder",
        options: [
            "A. wonder",
            "B. border",
            "C. ponder",
            "D. worry"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "/j/",
        answer: "C. suit",
        options: [
            "A. jalopy",
            "B. beige",
            "C. suit",
            "D. bay"
        ]
    },
    
    {
        question: "/z/",
        answer: "C. days",
        options: [
            "A. rice",
            "B. race",
            "C. days",
            "D. loose"
        ]
    },
    
    {
        question: "/æ/",
        answer: "B. plait",
        options: [
            "A. giraffe",
            "B. plait",
            "C. plant",
            "D. pass"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "/ʃ/",
        answer: "B. brochure",
        options: [
            "A. decision",
            "B. brochure",
            "C. scissors",
            "D. chasm"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "/ʧ/",
        answer: "B. clutch",
        options: [
            "A. champagne",
            "B. clutch",
            "C. nation",
            "D. non-chalant"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "/d/",
        answer: "D. bagged",
        options: [
            "A. slapped",
            "B. educate",
            "C. procedure",
            "D. bagged"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "/h/",
        answer: "A. hero",
        options: [
            "A. hero",
            "B. sheer",
            "C. honesty",
            "D. honorable"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "/L/",
        answer: "B. salvo",
        options: [
            "A. salmon",
            "B. salvo",
            "C. calm",
            "D. psalm"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "/f/",
        answer: "D. draught",
        options: [
            "A. of",
            "B. dough",
            "C. drought",
            "D. draught"
        ]
    }
]